export const data = [
    {
      question: "Which of the following correctly describes overloading of functions?",
      option1: "Virtual polymorphism",
      option2: "Transient polymorphism",
      option3: "Ad-hoc polymorphism",
      option4: "Pseudo polymorphism",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "How many instances of an abstract class can be created?",
      option1: "1",
      option2: "5",
      option3: "13",
      option4: "0",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
      option1: "Spam",
      option2: "Fake",
      option3: "Archived",
      option4: "Bin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the correct class of the object cout?",
      option1: "iostream",
      option2: "istream",
      option3: "ostream",
      option4: "ifstream",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following statement is incorrect?",
      option1: "Constructor is a member function of the class.",
      option2: "The compiler always provides a zero argument constructor.",
      option3: "It is necessary that a constructor in a class should always be public.",
      option4: "Both B and C.",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "A union that has no constructor can be initialized with another union of __________ type.",
      option1: "different",
      option2: "same",
      option3: "virtual",
      option4: "class",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following concept of oops allows compiler to insert arguments in a function call if it is not specified?",
      option1: "Call by value",
      option2: "Call by reference",
      option3: "Default arguments",
      option4: "Call by pointer",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following keyword is used to overload an operator?",
      option1: "overload",
      option2: "operator",
      option3: "friend",
      option4: "override",
      ans: 2,
    },
     {
      question: "Which of the following concepts means adding new components to a program as it runs?",
      option1: "Data hiding",
      option2: "Dynamic typing",
      option3: "Dynamic binding",
      option4: "Dynamic loading",
      ans: 4,
    },
     {
      question: "Which of the following statement is correct?",
      option1: "The order of the default argument will be right to left.",
      option2: "The order of the default argument will be left to right.",
      option3: "The order of the default argument will be alternate.",
      option4: "The order of the default argument will be random.",
      ans: 1,
    },
  ];
